<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>
	<!-- ================================ Childhood ====================== -->
	<AC_FrontierUpbringing.title>邊疆教養</AC_FrontierUpbringing.title>
	<AC_FrontierUpbringing.titleShort>移民</AC_FrontierUpbringing.titleShort>
	<AC_FrontierUpbringing.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef]在最近被發現宜居的偏遠殖民地長大。這使其有點難以融入人類生活。多虧這種艱辛以及把食物擺上餐桌的掙扎，[PAWN_pronoun]學會欣賞簡單的事物，並且從不迴避在田野或與穀倉動物相處的一天。</AC_FrontierUpbringing.baseDesc>

	<AC_UrbanUpbringing.title>城市教養</AC_UrbanUpbringing.title>
	<AC_UrbanUpbringing.titleShort>滾球</AC_UrbanUpbringing.titleShort>
	<AC_UrbanUpbringing.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef]在核心世界之一長大。作為一個低賤者，它的家庭剛好足夠遇到避免生活在貧民窟。由於從未吃過加工食品以外的東西，[PAWN_pronoun]在學校學習了人類歷史的廣泛教育。</AC_UrbanUpbringing.baseDesc>

	<AC_SlumDweller.title>貧民窟居民</AC_SlumDweller.title>
	<AC_SlumDweller.titleShort>貧民窟</AC_SlumDweller.titleShort>
	<AC_SlumDweller.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef]在人口眾多的工業世界眾多棚戶區的一個地方社區長大的。食物很難獲得且只能靠搜刮獲取，[PAWN_pronoun]使用許多方法來生存，並且沒有引起執法部門的太多注意。</AC_SlumDweller.baseDesc>

	<AC_DigitalUpbringing.title>digital upbringing</AC_DigitalUpbringing.title>
	<AC_DigitalUpbringing.titleShort>virtual</AC_DigitalUpbringing.titleShort>
	<AC_DigitalUpbringing.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] experienced sleeve death not long after their stack was integrated, and [PAWN_possessive] parents were unable to afford an appropriate sleeve. As such, [PAWN_pronoun] was given what little virtual lessons and experience as could be afforded and has developed insecurities and a lack of identity.</AC_DigitalUpbringing.baseDesc>

	<AC_EarlyResleeving.title>early resleeving</AC_EarlyResleeving.title>
	<AC_EarlyResleeving.titleShort>resleeved</AC_EarlyResleeving.titleShort>
	<AC_EarlyResleeving.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] experienced accidental sleeve death during [PAWN_possessive] early years and was given a new sleeve as per victim restitution. The sleeve was completely different in all aspects. The imbalance between the sleeve and the stack meant [PAWN_pronoun] experienced life in a chaotic manner.</AC_EarlyResleeving.baseDesc>

	<AC_RichAspirant.title>rich aspirant</AC_RichAspirant.title>
	<AC_RichAspirant.titleShort>aspirant</AC_RichAspirant.titleShort>
	<AC_RichAspirant.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] had a single encounter with someone rich during a charity event that impacted [PAWN_possessive] life. [PAWN_possessive] was willing to do whatever it took to also become equally rich. The viability of this dream might be somewhat difficult, as [PAWN_pronoun] wants to use the power to help others rather than hoard wealth.</AC_RichAspirant.baseDesc>

	<AC_PowerObsessed.title>power obsessed</AC_PowerObsessed.title>
	<AC_PowerObsessed.titleShort>obsessed</AC_PowerObsessed.titleShort>
	<AC_PowerObsessed.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] learned about the lifestyles of the rich and powerful early on and decided [PAWN_pronoun] wanted that experience as well. Having no scruples with illicit or morally ambiguous behaviour, [PAWN_pronoun] managed to work their way up the social hierarchy and managed to touch the lives of the powerful as part of their early career.</AC_PowerObsessed.baseDesc>

	<AC_CoreWorldRecruit.title>praetorian recruit</AC_CoreWorldRecruit.title>
	<AC_CoreWorldRecruit.titleShort>recruit</AC_CoreWorldRecruit.titleShort>
	<AC_CoreWorldRecruit.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was picked up at a young age by the core worlds military for displaying particular qualities that would make [PAWN_possessive] an uncompromising soldier. Most training having occurred in virtual and in special combat Sleeves, [PAWN_pronoun] proved a valuable asset for the Praetorians.</AC_CoreWorldRecruit.baseDesc>
	
	<!-- ================================ Adultdhood ====================== -->
	<AC_SettledColonist.title>settled colonist</AC_SettledColonist.title>
	<AC_SettledColonist.titleShort>colonist</AC_SettledColonist.titleShort>
	<AC_SettledColonist.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] once inhabited one of the remote Settled Worlds during its initial developmental stages and helped keep their colony running. Life was dull and uninteresting compared to living on a Rimworld, as [PAWN_pronoun] was always under the watchful eye of the local authorities.</AC_SettledColonist.baseDesc>

	<AC_SettledRefugee.title>settled refugee</AC_SettledRefugee.title>
	<AC_SettledRefugee.titleShort>refugee</AC_SettledRefugee.titleShort>
	<AC_SettledRefugee.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] managed to obtain transit to a remote settled world under a resettlement program. Fleeing from a life of danger and conflict, [PAWN_pronoun] hoped to start a new life without having to worry about raiders and criminals coming to take [PAWN_possessive] hard-earned belongings.</AC_SettledRefugee.baseDesc>

	<AC_SettledCivilian.title>settled civilian</AC_SettledCivilian.title>
	<AC_SettledCivilian.titleShort>urbanite</AC_SettledCivilian.titleShort>
	<AC_SettledCivilian.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew tired of the drab and boring lifestyle of living in cities ruled by the rich, rather than the local authorities. Disillusioned with the government failures, [PAWN_pronoun] took the first affordable transit off [PAWN_possessive] world in order to gain some semblance of control over [PAWN_possessive] life.</AC_SettledCivilian.baseDesc>

	<AC_VirtualAddict.title>virtual addict</AC_VirtualAddict.title>
	<AC_VirtualAddict.titleShort>addict</AC_VirtualAddict.titleShort>
	<AC_VirtualAddict.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] spent an astronomical amount of money on experiencing all that virtual reality could offer. Whether it was other worlds, blood arenas, sexperiences or the lives of meths, [PAWN_pronoun] was eventually forced to go cold-turkey when [PAWN_possessive] debtors started trying to collect what they were owed.</AC_VirtualAddict.baseDesc>

	<AC_RichOutcast.title>rich outcast</AC_RichOutcast.title>
	<AC_RichOutcast.titleShort>outcast</AC_RichOutcast.titleShort>
	<AC_RichOutcast.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] used to be rich and powerful before being cast out by their relatives for being an embarrassment. No longer privileged to obscene wealth and decadence, [PAWN_pronoun] has been forced to live as a lowly grounder outside of the core worlds.</AC_RichOutcast.baseDesc>

	<AC_PowerFanatic.title>power fanatic</AC_PowerFanatic.title>
	<AC_PowerFanatic.titleShort>fanatic</AC_PowerFanatic.titleShort>
	<AC_PowerFanatic.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] believes in the righteousness of the rich and powerful, that they are living, breathing gods among mere mortals and that with enough worship, [PAWN_pronoun] would be blessed to join their ranks. Naturally, [PAWN_pronoun] was discarded when no longer useful but that dogmatic faith remains.</AC_PowerFanatic.baseDesc>

	<AC_PraetorianSoldier.title>praetorian soldier</AC_PraetorianSoldier.title>
	<AC_PraetorianSoldier.titleShort>praetorian</AC_PraetorianSoldier.titleShort>
	<AC_PraetorianSoldier.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was part of the core world military forces and saw numerous battles on different worlds in different sleeves. Relying on reacclimation drugs, [PAWN_pronoun] was able to use many combat sleeves over time but has developed numerous social deficiencies.</AC_PraetorianSoldier.baseDesc>
</LanguageData>